George Brata

Frontend Web Developer





Summary

Versatile frontend web developer with broad experience using all kinds of JS frameworks, but my favorite stack (at the moment) is **Vue.js** / **Nuxt.js**. Very passionate about education, the Internet, and blockchain technology - and everything that connects the three.

Experience

Senior Vue.js Developer, SHE Information Technology

Apr 2021 - Mar 2022

My responsibilities were maintaining a web platform based on FirstSpirit CMS, creating new Vue.js components and providing support for multilingual content teams across the world.

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Vue.js Developer, Salt&Pepper

Worked with a remote Maltese team to build and deliver an online casino. We created new functionalities using a proprietary frontend framework built on top of Vue.js with Typescript.

Jul 2018 - Dec 2019

Frontend Web Developer, QCatalyst

Building, testing, deploying and maintaining responsive consumer-facing web applications for National Geographic using modern technologies like React, Redux, TailwindCSS, Webpack, Storybook and Jest.

Apr 2017 - Apr 2018

UI Developer, 3Pillar Global

Developed financial education learning modules for a US-based client in a React.js app. As a team, we worked with tools like Github, CircleCl, JIRA, Browserstack and Confluence to deliver high-quality readable code and documentation.

Jun 2016 - Apr 2017

Junior Web Developer, Yonder

Migrated a legacy app from Microsoft Silverlight to AngularJS and built the frontend of a completely new web app from scratch using Angular.js and Bulma CSS.

Feb 2016 - May 2016

Intern Web Development, Yonder

Learned the basics of web development - HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery. In the last month, we built a small web multiplayer game using Flask (a Python framework), Bootstrap, and SocketIO.

Feb 2016 - present

Trainer, Digital Kids Cluj-Napoca

In my spare time I teach children the computer skills they need to thrive in the 21st century, including the basics of programming, photo/video editing, robotics, web development and other digital abilities.

Education

2014 - 2015 2010 - 2014 Computer Science, *Babes-Bolyai University*, Cluj-Napoca Mathematics - Informatics, *Emanuil Gojdu* High School, Oradea

Why hire me?

Results-driven and people-oriented, I am feeling comfortable in any kind of healthy dev environment, either corporate or start-up. I get excited about crafting modern web applications and continuously delivering top-notch functionalities with warm UX. Beside my regular frontend developer job, over the last 6 years I have built several freelancing side-projects and I went to a dozen hackathons to train exactly those muscles.